Thumbiko Nyasulu

104 Cian Lea Swords, Rathbeale road, Co. Dublin. **Mobile:** 0858429584. **Email:** thumbikonyasulu@ymail.com **Linkedin:** www.linkedin.com/in/tivz

Currently a student in my Final Year of college enrolled in computer science infrastructure who is self-motivated, a team player who can work under pressure. I am available four days per week. I have a range of experience that has helped me to develop valuable skills such as clear communication, teamwork, adaptability and reliability.

EDUCATION

2013-2018	Leaving Cert (Secondary school), Colaiste Choilm Swords, Dublin
2018-2019	Computer systems and networks with Cybersecurity, Finglas West, Dublin
	7 Distinctions, 1 Merit.
2019-2023	BSc Computer Science Infrastructure, Technological University Dublin

WORK EXPERIENCE

June 2017- June 2021

Carlton Hotel Blanchardstown

Conference and Banqueting/Food and beverage assistant.

- Serving customers and dealing with their requests.
- Cash handling on the checkout.
- Welcomed visitors on arrival.
- Dealt with customer queries and customer complaints.

March 2022 – August 2022 IT Support Intern

Surecom, Greenogue Rathcoole Business Park, Dublin

- Worked with stakeholders in different departments
- Assist with the investigation & development of new applications and systems.
- Researched new tools/software to assist other business units.

SKILLS

- Quick learner, Adaptability.
- Excellent people skills
- Ability to work under pressure
- Customer service
- Cash and card transactions
- Excellent memory
- Organizational skills

- Time management
- Stocking and replenishing

INTERESTS/ACHIEVEMENTS

Technology:

- Keen interest in technology, particularly in software development.
- Regularly provide technical support for friends and family.
- Troubleshoot old laptops and mobiles for fun.

Sport:

• Attend basketball scrimmage sessions on a regular basis.

Content creation:

• Part of a YouTube group.

REFERENCES AVAILABLE ON REQUEST